

# Sai Kumar Student

nagubandisai40@gmail.com

9849210151

Hyderabad, India

linkedin.com/in/saikumar9436 in

github.com/nagubandisai40 (

I am self-motivated and Pursuing my degree at BV Raju Institute of Technology. I had worked on android app and Web development, very much interested in analyzing a huge amount of data and to extract the knowledge and insights from that data.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Technology** BV Raju Institute of Technology

06/2017 - Present

9.86/10

Intermediate

Sri Chaitanya Junior College

06/2015 - 05/2017

980/1000

SSC

Montessori English Medium School

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

vHelp\_2k18 (06/2018 – 07/2018) 🗗

 Developed an Android app which provides all the details regarding our college. (BVRITN).

Pay 1Rs (02/2019 – 03/2019) 🗗

 Website with payment gateway integrated. In this website the user need to pay 1 rupee in order to see the names of the people who all paid me.

Pay 1Rs (02/2019 – 03/2019) 🗗

Website with Payment gateway Integrated.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

The Sparks Foundation (Virtual)

05/2019 - 07/2019

- Designed a website with Payment Gateway Integrated.
- Worked on developing REST API by using SLIM Framework.

## Middle ware Framework To Access Multi-**Cloud Systems**

BVRIT Cloud Computing Center (Narsapur)

05/2019 - 07/2019

Worked on designing a middle ware framework for accessing multiple clouds.

### **SKILLS**



## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Qualified in Round 1 of TCS CodeVita Season 8. 🗹

Held on 28th June, 2019 - 13th July, 2019 and securing Rank 2020 from total participation of 55,654.

Digital Developer Conference: Cloud Native Track

The badge earner understands essential concepts related to the implementation of secure microservices applications in a multi-cloud environment. The badge earner has hands-on experience with deploying applications on Kubernetes.

Digital Developer Conference: Machine Learning Track 🗹

The badge earner understands the collaborative nature involved in the efficient practice of data science to address enterprise problems and leverage open source tooling. The badge earner has hands-on experience in creating explainable models.

#### CERTIFICATES

TSF Certificate of Completion 🗹

For an Outstanding contribution during the session (May 2019 to July 2019) of Graduate Rotational Internship Program at The Sparks Foundation on 17 July 2019.

Internshala Student Partner 11 🗹

For successfully completing the ISP11 Program with internshala during the period of September 2018 to November 2018.

#### LANGUAGES

**English** 

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Telugu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### INTERESTS

**Data Scientist** 

Android

Web Development